I have no money.
ليس لدي المال.
But my husband is rich.
لكن زوجي غني.
My husband is in charge of
زوجي هو المسؤول عن
the financial affairs of the Tianxing State.
الشؤون المالية لدولة تيانشينغ.
His name is Prince Yu.
اسمه الأمير يو.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Don't blame me for being unkind.
لا تلومني لكوني قاسياً.
Miss,
يفتقد،
I didn't touch you just now.
أنا لم ألمسك الآن.
Don't lie to me.
لا تكذب علي.
My spiritual lid
غطائي الروحي
My elbow hurts.
كوعي يؤلمني.
My whole body hurts.
كل جسدي يؤلمني.
My head hurts.
رأسي يؤلمني.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Let me take you to the hospital.
دعني آخذك إلى المستشفى.
No.
لا.
I'm going back to Xinghai City.
سأعود إلى مدينة Xinghai.
If you don’t see me off,
إذا كنت لا تراني ،
you can report to the police.
يمكنك إبلاغ الشرطة.
But someone rented my carriage.
لكن أحدهم استأجر عربتي.
It's okay.
حسنا.
You can send him home.
يمكنك إرساله إلى المنزل.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Sorry.
آسف.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Are you having a bad time
هل تمر بوقت سيء
She wants to go back to Xinghai City.
إنها تريد العودة إلى مدينة Xinghai.
Prince Yu.
الأمير يو.
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
What if I let her go
ماذا لو تركتها تذهب
what if she runs away again?
ماذا لو هربت مرة أخرى؟
Why are you running?
لماذا تجري؟
I have no money in my pocket.
ليس لدي نقود في جيبي.
But why are you here?
لكن لماذا انت هنا
I just want to go to Pingyuan City
أنا فقط أريد أن أذهب إلى مدينة بينغيوان
to buy some specialties that Madam likes.
لشراء بعض التخصصات التي تحبها سيدتي.
Really?
هل حقا؟
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
However,
لكن،
why do you look
لماذا تنظر
look so awkward?
تبدو محرجا جدا؟
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم.
I’m experiencing life.
أنا أعاني من الحياة.
Aren’t you going to Pingyuan City?
ألا تذهب إلى مدينة بينغيوان؟
Why are you still here?
لماذا لا تزال هنا؟
Okay.
تمام.
You can leave if you want.
يمكنك المغادرة إذا أردت.
Uncle Zhang.
العم تشانغ.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Okay.
تمام.
Your Excellency.
امتيازك.
The dishes and rooms
الأطباق والغرف
and rooms are ready.
والغرف جاهزة.
Please come in.
تفضل بالدخول.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Your lord is quite generous.
سيدك كريم جدا.
That's because our father-in-law has face.
هذا لأن والد زوجتنا لديه وجه.
I'm flattered.
أنا أشعر بالإطراء.
I'll eat with Her Ladyship first.
سوف آكل مع سيدتها أولاً.
I can't let Prince Yu know
لا يمكنني السماح للأمير يو بمعرفة
I'm not doing well these days.
أنا لا أقوم بعمل جيد هذه الأيام.
as if I can't live without him.
كأنني لا أستطيع العيش بدونه.
Madam, please.
سيدتي من فضلك.
I'm not hungry.
انا لست جائع.
I'll go to Uncle Zhang first.
سأذهب إلى العم تشانغ أولاً.
Madam, take a rest.
سيدتي ، خذ قسطا من الراحة.
My lord, you are back.
سيدي ، لقد عدت.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Why aren't you eating?
لماذا لا تأكل
I just took a bite.
لقد أخذت للتو قضمة.
The food is much worse than the last two days.
الغذاء أسوأ بكثير من اليومين الماضيين.
I left it outside the window.
تركته خارج النافذة.
Madam, what is this?
سيدتي ما هذا؟
Nothing.
لا شيئ.
The window is a trash can.
النافذة عبارة عن سلة مهملات.
I threw it in the trash can.
رميته في سلة المهملات.
There's nothing to see.
لا يوجد شيء لتراه.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Nothing.
لا شيئ.
It's just that Her Ladyship was careless.
إنها فقط أن سيادتها كانت مهملة.
I forgot to throw out a grain of rice.
لقد نسيت أن أتخلص من حبة أرز.
Since you can't eat it,
بما أنك لا تستطيع أكله ،
I'll get some desserts tomorrow.
سأحضر بعض الحلويات غدا.
Eunuch.
الخصي.
The room is ready.
الغرفة جاهزة.
Here's the key.
هذا هو المفتاح.
Only
فقط
one room left?
غادرت غرفة واحدة؟
My lord,
ربي،
There are too many guests today.
يوجد الكثير من الضيوف اليوم.
There's only one room left.
لم يتبق سوى غرفة واحدة.
But...
لكن...
there are two of us.
هناك اثنين منا.
Can we have another room?
هل يمكننا الحصول على غرفة أخرى؟
To be honest,
لأكون صريحا،
I really can't spare any time.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع توفير أي وقت.
Besides, you and your wife...
الى جانب ذلك ، أنت وزوجتك ...
That's it.
هذا هو.
Let's
دعونا
as usual.
كل عادة.
Madam is afraid of the cold.
سيدتي تخاف من البرد.
Please prepare two more beddings.
يرجى تحضير سريرين إضافيين.
Okay, please wait a moment.
حسنًا ، من فضلك انتظر لحظة.
It's better when Prince Yu was here.
إنه أفضل عندما كان الأمير يو هنا.
Although I've suffered a little,
على الرغم من أنني عانيت قليلاً ،
but you don't have to suffer.
لكن ليس عليك أن تعاني.
You know how to feel sorry for yourself.
أنت تعرف كيف تشعر بالأسف على نفسك.
You even know to add a blanket for yourself.
أنت تعرف حتى أن تضيف بطانية لنفسك.
I'm not as good as you.
أنا لست جيدًا مثلك.
I have to take care of myself.
يجب أن أعتني بنفسي.
You...
أنت...
Madam.
سيدتي.
Did you take care of the child?
هل اعتنيت بالطفل؟
The owner told me there was no extra pillow today.
أخبرني المالك أنه لا توجد وسادة إضافية اليوم.
May I
ربما أنا
borrow your child again?
تقترض طفلك مرة أخرى؟
Can I
هل استطيع
lend me your child's pillow?
اقرضني وسادة طفلك؟
You...
أنت...
How dare you mess with me?
كيف تجرؤ على العبث معي؟
You've worked hard today.
لقد عملت بجد اليوم.
I'll go buy some stitches
سأذهب لشراء بعض الغرز
to sew your shoes.
لخياطة حذائك.
It's windy.
الطقس عاصف.
It's late.
الوقت متاخر.
I wonder
انا اتعجب
went to buy stitches.
ذهب لشراء غرز.
It's still windy.
لا يزال الجو عاصفًا.
Thank you, my lord.
شكرا لك يا سيدي.
My lord.
ربي.
Do we still need a carriage tomorrow?
هل ما زلنا بحاجة إلى عربة غدًا؟
Thank you, Uncle Zhang.
شكرا لك العم تشانغ.
I don't think I need it tomorrow.
لا أعتقد أنني بحاجة إليه غدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
My lord.
ربي.
Are you still staying tomorrow?
هل مازلت تقيم غدا؟
Of course.
بالتاكيد.
But
لكن
It's still a room.
لا تزال غرفة.